In the 2022.4.2 version, we improved the conflict processing function of GPU simulation,
which allows for stable simulation when simulating the clothing of multi-layered plate.
In addition, the conflict processing between the plate and the virtual model can also be run smoothly to increase the efficiency of the work.
Let's take a closer look at the improvements through the example.
Let's take a look at the UI changes in the software interface.
Since GPU simulation has been improved and expanded the scope of use, we have improved the menu of simulation functions.
First, add the animation used when recording animation, complete, image.
In addition, add the menu for setting CPU and GPU options at the bottom of the simulation type.
It is allowed to set CPU and GPU options for ordinary, test and animation simulation respectively.
When the GPU option is set, the simulation icons are displayed as empty keys.
Next, let's compare the use of GPU and GPU.
In order to make a clear comparison, you can click on the main menu to set the display environment display real speed,
to display the information and FPS speed of the used version at the bottom left of the 3D window.
First, compare the simulation speed of normal speed and default, on the left is GPU and on the right is CPU.
You can see that in terms of speed, the speed of GPU simulation is much faster.
Next, we will use the test穿 to simulate.
Similarly, we can see that GPU simulation is much faster than CPU simulation.
Please note that GPU simulation speed may be due to the performance of the graphics card.
After choosing GPU simulation, we can pull the board at the 3D window to observe the stability of the simulation.
You can see that even if the board is multi-layer, it can also be simulated in a stable way.
Next, we will demonstrate the process of using GPU simulation in animation mode to record the process of having multi-layer board clothing.
After selecting GPU simulation, we can pull the board at the 3D window to observe the stability of the simulation.
You can see that even if the board is multi-layer, it can also be simulated in a stable way.
When the strength of Agreed loss of factor is relatively small and the number of boards and layers is можете more.
It is much faster and more stable to use GPU simulation than before.
However, this may also be due to the performance of the graphics card.
It should be noted that GPU simulation is currently only applicable to ordinary clothing simulation, not including wool products.
In addition, it is not currently applicable to secondary simulation and software model simulation.
In addition to improving the speed of simulation, due to the improvement of conflict processing, the accuracy of GPU simulation has also been improved,
and when using GPU simulation, it can also get the same result as the CPU simulation result.
In addition, please note that when saving project files, the option of not saving the processor is not selected.
For example, when saving this file, the CPU is selected.
In the test mode,
the GPU simulation mode is changed to the GPU normal mode in the software, and when the file is opened again,
it will be changed to the processor option selected at this time.
However, the normal test mode and animation simulation options are saved in the file mode and become the test mode.
After improvement, the GPU simulation can be stabilized and quickly simulated.
Welcome to experience GPU simulation.
Thank you for your attention.
Please write your feelings and suggestions in the message area.